# **MARCUS JENNY**

DIGITAL MARKETING

### **Summary**

A Digital Marketing professional with more than 6 years of experience in different areas of Campaigns and Strategy, Conversion optimization, SEO specialist, PPC executive/specialist, Social media expert, Email marketing, Mobile Marketing, Data Analysis and Content Marketing.

## Experience

#### **Digital Marketing Specialist**

Amazon - London, UK Oct 2017 - Present

Focus on supporting Amazon sellers regarding Digital Marketing with traffic generation, conversions and sales:

- Guiding the sellers to optimize product details for search.
- Work to Continually Improving the local seller performance.
- Increased sales by 20% YoY by monitoring and optimizing all Amazon Marketing activities.
- Increased on average 5% in conversion rate by optimizing the UX on product pages and landing pages of the e-Commerce application.
- Setting up, monitoring and evaluating 3 (average per quarter) local Digital Marketing campaigns in collaboration with an external agency.

#### Digital Marketing Manager

Morrisons - London, UK Jul 2016 - Sep 2017

Focus on stimulating online sales & marketing for Norton in the Benelux and Nordics and responsible for converting traffic on our partner websites to sales for Norton:

- Launched the first social campaign with a retail partner.
- Collaborated with 3 Field Marketing Specialist to ensure an excellent CX in store and online
- Analyze marketing data and develop insights with the aim of identifying business needs and new opportunities
- Negotiated, planned and implemented new marketing programs with more than 15 partners
- Produced high-quality, effective marketing messages and promotions every quarter

### **Projects**

2015 Black Friday Marketing Digital Marketing Manager Jan 2015 - Present

Responsible for creating, managing and expanding the presence of

#### Contact

marcus.jenny@gmail.com 123 45 67 89 10 London, United Kingdom linkedin.com/in/marcus.jenny

#### Skills

- Google Analytics & Adobe
- Project Management
- Digital Marketing
- Advise Marketing teams
- Social Media Marketing
- Email Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Mobile Marketing

### Language

English
French
Italian
Chinese

## Awards

2019 Most Valuable Player Award Amazon 2019-09-19

### Certification

Certified Google Analytics & AdWords 2018

Certified Digital Marketing University of Westminster London 2016 the 2015 Black Friday Sales via Facebook, Instagram and other strategically relevant online channels:

- Increased Facebook involvement with 840% via video advertising campaigns.
- Developed effective multi-platform marketing plan that boosted sales for company clients.
- Managing the content calendar for Social Media.
- Collaborate with local external partners, including local media and suppliers.

## Education

Master's in Business Administration [Marketing] University of West London Sep 2014 - Mar 2016

Bacherlor's in Business Administration London School of Business and Finance Sep 2010 - Aug 2014

#### Referance

Will be produced on request